A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, International Division, Middle East and Africa, Tunis, Tunisia Field Office Files FA645
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Agriculture, 1962-1965, 1970-1975; I
  - Agriculture -- General -- Correspondence -- Morocco, 1969-1972 (Box 1)
  - Agriculture -- General -- Correspondence -- Tunisia, 1968-1972 (Box 1)
  - Agriculture -- General -- Fertilizer Situation, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Agriculture -- General -- (World) Food Situation, 1973-1975 (Box 1)
  - Agriculture -- General -- Other Agencies, 1968-1970 (Box 1)
  - Agriculture -- General -- Other Agencies, 1970-1972 (Box 1)
  - Agriculture -- General -- Other Agencies -- OLC -- Development from Below Field Trip/Workshop (Ethiopia, October 1973), 1973-1974 (Box 1)
  - Agriculture -- General -- Program Strategy Review, 1973-1974 (Box 1)
  - Agriculture -- Institut de Technologie Agricole -- Mostaganem, 1971-1976 (Box 1)
  - Agriculture -- Morocco -- Bureau Pedagogique -- Rabat Reports, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
  - Agriculture -- Morocco -- Bureau Pedagogique -- Rabat Reports (1/2), 1970-1971 (Box 2)
  - Agriculture -- Morocco -- Bureau Pedagogique -- Rabat Reports (2/2), 1970-1971 (Box 2)
  - Agriculture -- Morocco -- Bureau Pedagogique -- Rabat, Aug 1970-Dec 1972 (Box 2)
  - Agriculture -- Project Evaluations -- Handwritten Notes (Box 2)
  - Agriculture -- Project Proposals -- Association of Faculties of Agriculture in Africa (AFAA), 1973-1974 (Box 2)
  - Agriculture -- Project Proposals -- Rice -- Algeria, Morocco, and North Africa (other countries), 1973-1974 (Box 2)
  - Agriculture -- Project Proposals -- Training of Tunisian Mexican Wheat Extension Workers, 1971-1974 (Box 2)
  - Agriculture -- Training of Tunisian Mexican Wheat Extension Workers (Borgo-a-Mozzano, June 17-July 13, 1974) -- Reports and Results, 1974-1975 (Box 2)
  - Agriculture -- Tunisia -- Recyclage Center (#690-0505), 1970 (Box 2)
  - Agriculture -- Visit to Australia (Summer 1973) -- Tunisian and Algerian Officials (Box 2)
  - Agriculture -- "Vocational Agricultural Education in Tunisia and the Training of Intermediate Agricultural Cadres" by B.G. Moussouros (French and English versions), May 1970 (Box 2)
  - Agriculture -- "Vocational Agricultural Education in Tunisia and the Training of Intermediate Agricultural Cadres" by B.G. Moussouros and Notes Re: Agricultural Training Centers, 1970 (Box 2)
- Development Planning, 1961-1977; II
  - Development Planning -- Center for Research on Economic Development, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Development Planning -- Economic -- Tunisia -- Movement Jeunes Science Tunisie, Aug 1973 (Box 3)
  - Development Planning -- Public Management Review, 1973 (Box 3)
  - Development Planning and Administration -- General -- Information, 1969-1972 (Box 3)
  - Development Planning and Administration-- General -- Correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box 3)
  - Development Planning -- Report -- Notes on the Direction of Future Tunisian Planning and Possible Planning Assistance, Jul 1970 (Box 3)
  - Development Planning -- Report -- An Approach to Manpower Planning, Jul 1970 (Box 3)
  - Development Planning -- Social Science, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Development Planning -- General -- Other Agencies, Jan-Jul 1973 (Box 3)
  - Development Planning -- General -- Other Agencies -- L'Institut Atlantique/Instituto Affari Internazionali, 1972 (Box 3)
  - Development Planning -- General -- Other Agencies -- Resesarch Project on the Migration and Return of Professionals ("Brain Drain"), 1971 (Box 3)
  - Development Planning -- General -- Other Agencies -- Urban Studies Information, 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - Development Planning and Management -- General -- Other Agencies, 1973-1974 (Box 3)
  - Development Planning and Management -- General Information (II), 1973 (Box 3)
  - Development Planning -- Schools of Public Administration (Algeria, Morocco, Tunisia), 1966-1969 (Box 3)
  - Development Planning and Administration -- General -- Reports, 1968-1972 (Box 4)
  - CAFRAD -- African Training and Research Center in Administration for Development, 1964-1968 (Box 4)
  - Development and Planning -- Public Administration -- General, 1961-1969 (Box 4)
  - Population and Development Policy --Ford Foundation/Rockefeller Research Program, 1977 (Box 4)
  - Development Planning and Management -- General -- Reports -- Simmons Report, May 20, 1968 (Box 4)
  - Development Management and Planning -- Correspondence II, 1973-1974 (Box 5)
  - Development Management and Planning -- Correspondence III, 1974-1976 (Box 5)
  - Organisation Maghrebine de Gestion (OMG), 1975-1976 (Box 5)
  - Development and Management -- Conferences -- First Maghrebian Conference on Training in Enterprises, 1975 (Box 5)
  - Development Planning and Management -- Conferences and Seminars -- EFMD Conference/Turin, May 19-22, 1974 (Box 5)
  - Development Planning and Management -- Conferences and Seminars -- Executive Seminar on Employment Strategies, Washington, Oct 24, 1974 (Box 5)
  - Development Planning and Management -- Conferences and Seminars -- Miscellaneous, 1968-1976 (Box 5)
  - Development Planning and Management -- Project Proposal -- INPED, Algeria, 1973-1974 (Box 5)
  - Development Planning and Management -- Public Management Program Development -- Richard S. Roberts, Jr. -- Visit to the U.S., Summer 1973 (Box 5)
  - Development and Planning -- Historia -- Algeria, 1972 (Box 5)
  - Development and Planning -- Project Proposals (Information Sheet and Miscellaneous), 1974 (Box 5)
  - Project Proposal -- Possible Consultancy for I.S.G. Dr. Khemakhem, 1974 (Box 5)
  - Development Planning and Management -- General Specified Files -- Management Strategy Review, Sep 1973 (Box 5)
  - National Institute of Productivity Management and Enterprise -- Training -- Tunisia, 1968-1971 (Box 5)
  - Development and Planning -- Urban Renewal -- Morocco, 1968-1972 (Box 5)
  - CODESRIA and Educational Development -- Memoranda re: Activities, Meetings, etc., 1972-1973 (Box 5)
- Education, 1960-1978; III
  - Center for Economic and Social Research -- University of Tunis, 1966-1968 (Box 6)
  - Center for Economic and Social Research -- Reports I, 1961-1967 (Box 6)
  - Center for Economic and Social Research (1/2), 1961-1964 (Box 6)
  - Center for Economic and Social Research (CERS) (2/2), 1968 (Box 6)
  - Education -- Assisting Educational and Cultural Development, 1974 (Box 6)
  - Education -- English Language in Tunisia, 1974 (Box 6)
  - Education -- Discretionary Grants -- Faculte de Lettres, Tunis -- English Plavers, 1969-1970 (Box 6)
  - Education and Research -- Discretionary Grants -- Ecole des Beaux Arts, Tunis, 1969-1970 (Box 6)
  - Education -- Carthage English Seminar, 1969-1973 (Box 6)
  - Education -- CAFRAD, 1970-1973 (Box 6)
  - Education -- Discretionry Award -- English Training, 1969-1970 (Box 6)
  - Education -- Discretionary Awards -- Representative's Contingency Fund, 1968-1969
  - Education -- General and Textbook Project, 1971-1974 (Box 7)
  - Education -- Ministry of Foreign Affairs -- CERES, 1975-1977 (Box 7)
  - Education -- Revue D'Histoire Maghrebine, 1975-1977 (Box 7)
  - Education -- IPSI, 1975-1977 (Box 7)
  - Stambouli, 1976-1977 (Box 7)
  - Education -- Textbook Project, 1971 (Box 7)
  - Education and Research -- Conferences and Seminars -- Miscellaneous, 1969-1971 (Box 7)
  - Education -- Summer Seminar, 1968 (Box 7)
  - Education and Research -- General Correspondence I, 1970-1972 (Box 7)
  - Education and Research -- General Correspondence II, Jan-Aug 1973 (Box 7)
  - Education -- General -- Seminars and Conferences, 1973 (Box 7)
  - Education and Research -- General Information I, 1969-1972 (Box 7)
  - Education and Research -- General Information II, 1973 (Box 7)
  - Education and Research -- General Information III, 1974 (Box 7)
  - Education and Research -- General Reports I, 1969 (Box 7)
  - Education and Research -- General Reports III, 1973 (Box 7)
  - Education and Research -- General Reports IV, 1974 (Box 7)
  - Travel and Study -- TOEFL/Algeria -- Kouloughli, 1971-1972 (Box 7)
  - Education -- Travel and Study -- General File, 1970-1971 (Box 7)
  - Education -- General Information -- History, 1967-1973 (Box 8)
  - Education -- General -- Restrospective Study & Harrison/Fox Correspondence, 1973 (Box 8)
  - Education -- Instituts de Technologies, n.d. (Box 8)
  - Education -- Migration -- Iranians, 1972 (Box 8)
  - Education -- Report -- Ford Foundation Consulting Mission in re: Request from Algerian Ministry of Higher Education, 1975 (Box 8)
  - Education and Research -- Reports -- Project Proposals -- Social Sciences/Migration of Scholars -- Micaud, 1973-1975 (Box 8)
  - Education -- Special Topics - -Institut de Presse Tunis, 1973-1975 (Box 8)
  - Education and Research -- English for Special Purposes -- Linguistic Institute, 1974-1975 (Box 8)
  - Education -- Tunis -- National School of Administration -- Reports II, 1968-1973 (Box 8)
  - Education -- Tunis -- National School of Administration -- Correspondence I, 1962-1966 (Box 8)
  - Education -- Tunis -- National School of Administration -- Correspondence II, 1967-1974 (Box 8)
  - Education -- General -- Information -- Tunisia, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
  - Education -- General Information -- Algeria, 1971-1975 (Box 8)
  - Education -- Algeria -- Recruitment Project -- Professors, 1975-1976 (Box 8)
  - Education and Research -- Algerian Language Institute -- Survey, 1975-1976 (Box 8)
  - Education -- Report -- English Language Teaching in Algeria, Sep 1975 (Box 8)
  - Education -- Algeria -- Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 8)
  - Education -- Algeria -- Scholarships, 1962-1965 (Box 8)
  - Algers Linguistics Project, 1968 (Box 8)
  - Algers Linguistics Project, 1969 (Box 8)
  - Algers Linguistics Project, 1970 (Box 8)
  - Education and Research -- General Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 9)
  - Education -- General -- Other Agencies -- American Friends of the Middle East and/or Maghreb -- Mrs. Patricia Payne, Jan 1974 (Box 9)
  - Education and Research -- General -- Other Information, 1974-1976 (Box 9)
  - Education -- Conference -- Social Sciences -- North Africa, 1976 (Box 9)
  - Education and Research -- Conferences and Seminars -- Miscellaneous, 1974-1975 (Box 9)
  - Education -- Tunisian Desert Biome Project -- Novikoff, 1974-1978 (Box 9)
  - Education -- General Information -- Morocco, 1972-1976 (Box 9)
  - Education -- Fundamental Arabic Project -- Seminar and Proposal (Olson, Beirut), 1973-1974 (Box 9)
  - Education -- General -- Other Agencies -- Overseas Liason Committee -- American Council on Education, 1974-1975 (Box 9)
  - Education -- General -- Other Agencies II, 1973 (Box 9)
  - Education -- English for Special Purposes Conference -- Hannamet, Tunisia, Feb 25-28, 1975 (Box 9)
  - Education -- ELT Project -- Correspondence, May 1973-Jan 1974 (Box 9)
  - Education -- English Language Textbook Development for Secondary Schools -- Reports (E1690-0742) (1/2), Jan-Dec 1972 (Box 9)
  - Education -- English Language Textbook Development for Secondary Schools -- Reports (E1690-0742) (2/2), Jan-Dec 1972 (Box 9)
  - Education -- English Language Textbook Development for Secondary Schools -- (690-0742) -- Reports (1/2), 1969-1972 (Box 9)
  - Education -- English Language Textbook Development for Secondary Schools -- (690-0742) -- Reports (2/2), 1969-1972 (Box 9)
  - Education -- English Language Textbook Development for Secondary Schools -- (729-0046) -- Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 9)
  - Education -- English Language Textbook Development for Secondary Schools -- Financial, Jun 1974-1975 (Box 9)
  - Education -- ELT Project, 1960-1978; III.1 (Box 10)
    - ELT Project -- Requests for Grant Action, 1963-1967 (Box 10)
    - ELT Project -- Summer Seminar, 1970 (Box 10)
    - Education - English Language Textbook (ELT) Project -- Correspondence IV, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
    - ELT Project -- Textbook Project IV bis -- Summer Course -- Bizerta, 1973 (Box 10)
    - ELT Project -- Textbook Project -- Tunisia -- IV bis -- Seminars, 1971-1972 (Box 10)
    - ELT Project -- Group Study Tours, 1973 (Box 10)
    - ELT Project -- Textbook Project Tunisia -- Budget, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
    - ELT Project -- Algeria -- R.M. Payne Trip, May 1974 (Box 10)
    - Report -- The Economy of the Maghreb, 1963 (Box 10)
    - Study of the Creation of the Tunisian University, n.d. (Box 10)
    - La Situation de L'Enseignement en Tunisie 1958-1964, May-Jun 1964 (Box 10)
    - A Ten Year Prospect of School Attendance (Box 10)
    - Situation Scolaire, Jun 1961 (Box 10)
    - New Conception of Education in Tunisia 1958-1959, [1960] (Box 10)
    - Situation de L'enseignement, 1962-1963 (Box 10)
    - Universite de Tunis -- Fondation et Premieres Realisations, 1960-1961 (Box 10)
    - English Language Education in North Africa -- English Textbook Project (DAP 759-0800) (1/2), 1974-1978 (Box 10)
    - English Language Education in North Africa -- English Textbook Project (DAP 759-0800) (2/2), 1974-1978 (Box 10)
    - Education -- English for Special Purposes Conference in Hammamet (1/2), 1974-1975 (Box 10)
    - Education -- English for Special Purposes Conference in Hammamet (2/2), 1974-1975 (Box 10)
    - Linguistics -- Summer Seminar -- Algeria, Tunisia, Morocco, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
- General Reports, 1960-1973; IV
  - General -- Information -- North Africa Review, 1972 (Box 11)
  - Middle East and Africa (MEA) Program Report, 1973 (Box 11)
  - General -- Reports -- Quarterly (Tunis Field Office), 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - Quarterly Reports -- Tunis, 1972 (Box 11)
  - General -- Reports -- Algeria/Tunisia/Morocco, 1968-1971 (Box 11)
  - General -- Reports -- Administrative Reports, 1966-1970 (Box 11)
  - General -- Reports -- Evaluation Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 11)
  - North African Program Annual Report, Nov 1970 (Box 11)
  - North African Program Annual Report, 1971 (Box 11)
  - North African Program Annual Report, 1972 (Box 11)
  - Ford Foundation Annual Reports 1969 Distribution, 1970 (Box 11)
  - Ford Foundation Annual Reports 1970 Distribution, 1971 (Box 11)
  - Ford Foundation Annual Reports 1971 Distribution, Summer 1972 (Box 11)
  - General -- Reports -- Annual Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 11)
  - General -- Government Relations -- Tunisia, 1968-1971 (Box 11)
  - General -- Government Relations -- Algeria, 1965-1971 (Box 11)
  - General -- Government Relations -- Morocco, 1960-1972 (Box 11)
  - Tunis Field Office -- Local Ford Foundation Correspondence Left by George Sheldon, 1968-1970 (Box 11)
  - Tunis Field Office -- Inter-office Memoranda, 1969-1971 (Box 11)
  - Tunis Field Office -- Financial Management Reviews and Internal Accounting Control -- Price Waterhouse & Co., 1963-1971 (Box 11)
  - Special Reports -- Comptroller's Office, 1970-1971 (Box 11)
- General -- Subject Files, 1965-1971; V
  - International Division Conference -- Mexico -- Representatives Meeting, 1968-1969 (Box 12)
  - International Division -- Representatives Meeting -- Nairobi, 1968 (Box 12)
  - International Division -- Representatives Meeting -- Tunis, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Education -- New Delhi Conference, Oct 1971 (Box 12)
  - International Division -- New Delhi Conference -- Discussion Paper, Oct 1971 (Box 12)
- General Correspondence, 1963-1974; VI
  - Correspondence -- General -- Other Agencies -- Miscellaneous, Jan 1973-Dec 1974 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence -- General -- Other Agencies -- Divers, 1970-1972 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence -- General -- Other Agencies -- Morocco, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence -- General -- Other Agencies -- Tunisia, 1968-1972 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence -- General -- Other Agencies -- Algeria, 1972 (Box 12)
  - General -- Conferences and Seminars -- MEA Economics Program Advisors Conference -- New York, Sep 1971 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence -- Administrative Conference -- Nairobi, Jul 1969 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence -- General -- Non-Program Conferences -- Divers, 1969 (Box 12)
  - Chronological Correspondence -- Algiers, 1971 (Box 12)
  - Marshall, R., 1969-1970 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence -- Brown, 1969-1971 (Box 12)
  - Brucher, Mr. Felix, 1970-1971 (Box 12)
  - General -- LeMelle, Wilbert J. -- General, Apr-Sep 1973 (Box 12)
  - General -- LeMelle, Wilbert J. -- General, Oct-Dec 1973 (Box 12)
  - General -- LeMelle, Wilbert -- Personal, 1973 (Box 12)
  - General -- Guillaume deSpoelberch's Fairwell Letters, 1973 (Box 12)
  - Chronological Correspondence, Feb 16-Sep 30, 1963 (Box 13)
  - Chronological Correspondence, Oct 1963-Mar 1964 (Box 13)
  - Chronological Correspondence, Apr-Sep 1964 (Box 13)
  - Chronological Correspondence, Oct 1964-Apr 1965 (Box 13)
  - Chronological Correspondence (1/2), Jan-Apr 1968 (Box 13)
  - Chronological Correspondence (2/2), Jan-Apr 1968 (Box 13)
  - Chronological Correspondence (1/2), May-Aug 1968 (Box 13)
  - Chronological Correspondence (2/2), May-Aug 1968 (Box 13)
  - Chronological Correspondence (1/2), Aug-Dec 1968 (Box 13)
  - Chronological Correspondence (2/2), Aug-Dec 1968 (Box 13)
  - Chronological Correspondence (1/2), Jan-Mar 1969 (Box 13)
  - Chronological Correspondence (2/2), Jan-Mar 1969 (Box 13)
  - Chronological Correspondence (1/2), Apr-Jun 1969 (Box 13)
  - Chronological Correspondence (2/2), Apr-Jun 1969 (Box 13)
  - Chronological Correspondence (1/2), Jul-Oct 1969 (Box 13)
  - Chronological Correspondence (2/2), Jul-Oct 1969 (Box 13)
  - Administrative Chronological Correspondence, Jan-Oct 1973 (Box 14)
  - Program Chronological Correspondence, Jan-Jun 1973 (Box 14)
  - Program Chronological Correspondence, Jul-Dec 1973 (Box 14)
  - Chronological Correspondence Files -- Algeria, 1973 (Box 14)
- Population, 1962-1976; VII
  - Algeria Family Planning Program -- Demography Project I, 1964-1965 (Box 15)
  - Algeria Family Planning Program -- Demography Project II, 1964-1966 (Box 15)
  - Algeria Family Planning Program -- Demography Project III, 1966-1967 (Box 15)
  - Algeria Family Planning Program -- Demography Project IV, 1967-1968 (Box 15)
  - Algeria Family Planning Program -- Demographic Assistance, Jan 1968-Feb 1970 (Box 15)
  - Population -- Demographic Assistance in Algeria -- Reports I, 1971-1973 (Box 15)
  - Population -- Demographic Assistance in Algeria -- Reports II, 1973 (Box 15)
  - Population -- Demographic Assistance in Algeria -- II, 1970-1971 (Box 15)
  - Population -- Demographic Assistance in Algeria -- III (1/2), 1971-1973 (Box 15)
  - Population -- Demographic Assistance in Algeria -- III (2/2), 1971-1973 (Box 15)
  - Population -- Demographic Assistance in Algeria -- IV, 1973-1974 (Box 15)
  - Population -- Demography Algeria -- "La Republique" Article (June 23, 1973) -- Translation/Distribution (June 1974), 1973-1974 (Box 15)
  - Population -- General -- Migration -- Algeria, 1973-1974 (Box 15)
  - Algeria Family Planning Report ("Les Imperatifs d'une Planification Familiale en Algerie") by Pierre Pradervand et al., Apr 1966 (Box 15)
  - Survey of Family Planning Knowledge, Attitudes, and Practice in Algeria (#670-0134), 1967-1970 (Box 15)
  - Family Planning and Demography -- Maghreb (North Africa) -- Reports (1/3), 1962-1969 (Box 16)
  - Family Planning and Demography -- Maghreb (North Africa) -- Reports (2/3), 1962-1969 (Box 16)
  - Family Planning and Demography -- Maghreb (North Africa) -- Reports (3/3), 1962-1969 (Box 16)
  - Population -- Kingdom of Morocco -- National Family Planning Program -- Reports I, 1965-1967 (Box 16)
  - Population -- Kingdom of Morocco -- National Family Planning Program -- Reports II, 1967-1970 (Box 16)
  - Population -- Kingdom of Morocco -- National Family Planning Program -- Reports III, 1970-1971 (Box 16)
  - Population -- Kingdom of Morocco -- National Family Planning Program -- Reports IV (1/2), 1971-1972 (Box 16)
  - Population -- Kingdom of Morocco -- National Family Planning Program -- Reports IV (2/2), 1971-1972 (Box 16)
  - Population -- Kingdom of Morocco -- National Family Planning Program -- Reports V, 1972-1973 (Box 16)
  - Population -- Kingdom of Morocco -- National Family Planning Program -- Correspondence, Jun 1971-Dec 1973 (Box 16)
  - "Family Planning in Morocco, 1965-1972: The Role of Ford Foundation and Population Council Assistance" by Richard S. Roberts, Jr. (1/2), Dec 1972 (Box 16)
  - "Family Planning in Morocco, 1965-1972: The Role of Ford Foundation and Population Council Assistance" by Richard S. Roberts, Jr. (2/2, second copy), Dec 1972 (Box 16)
  - Family Planning in Tunisia, 1963 (Box 17)
  - National Program in Family Planning -- Tunisia -- Correspondence Vol. I (63-270A), Mar 1962-Dec 1964 (Box 17)
  - National Program in Family Planning -- Tunisia -- Correspondence Vol. II (63-270A), Jan 1965-Jun 1968 (Box 17)
  - National Program in Family Planning -- Tunisia -- Correspondence Vol. III (63-270A) (1/2), Jun 1969-Apr 1970 (Box 17)
  - National Program in Family Planning -- Tunisia -- Correspondence Vol. III (63-270A) (2/2), Jun 1969-Apr 1970 (Box 17)
  - National Program in Family Planning -- Tunisia -- Correspondence Vol. IV (63-270A), May 1970-May 1971 (Box 17)
  - National Program in Family Planning -- Tunisia -- Correspondence Vol. V (63-270A), Jun 1971-Apr 1973 (Box 17)
  - Tunisia -- National Program in Family Planning -- Reports I, 1962-1966 (Box 17)
  - Tunisia -- National Program in Family Planning -- Reports II, 1967-1968 (Box 17)
  - Tunisia -- National Program in Family Planning -- Reports III, 1969-1970 (Box 17)
  - Tunisia -- National Program in Family Planning -- Reports IV, Apr 1970-Apr 1971 (Box 17)
  - Tunisia -- National Program in Family Planning -- Reports V, May 1971-Jan 1972 (Box 18)
  - Tunisia -- National Program in Family Planning -- Reports VI, Feb 1972-Jul 1972 (Box 18)
  - Tunisia -- National Program in Family Planning -- Reports VII, Aug 1972-Dec 1973 (Box 18)
  - Population -- Tunisia -- National Program in Family Planning, 1967-1969 (Box 18)
  - Population -- Republic of Tunisia -- National Program in Family Planning, 1970-1975 (Box 18)
  - North African Regional Program in Family Planning, 1973-1976 (Box 18)
  - North African Regional Program in Family Planning (690-0657), 1969-1973 (Box 18)
  - North African Regional Program in Family Planning (690-0657) -- Correspondence (1/2), 1973-1976 (Box 18)
  - North African Regional Program in Family Planning (690-0657) -- Correspondence (2/2), 1973-1976 (Box 18)
  - North African Regional Program in Family Planning (690-0657) -- Reports, 1970-1973 (Box 18)
  - North African Regional Program in Family Planning (690-0657) -- General, Reports, 1974-1976 (Box 18)
  - Family Planning and Demography -- Tunisia, Morocco, Algeria -- General Reports (1/3), 1971-1972 (Box 19)
  - Family Planning and Demography -- Tunisia, Morocco, Algeria -- General Reports (2/3), 1971-1972 (Box 19)
  - Family Planning and Demography -- Tunisia, Morocco, Algeria -- General Reports (3/3), 1971-1972 (Box 19)
  - Family Planning and Demography -- Tunisia, Morocco, Algeria -- General Reports, 1974 (Box 19)
  - "The Ford Foundation/Population Council North African Population Program in Retrospect: 1963-1975" by Alain Marcoux, Dec 1975 (Box 19)
  - Population Evaluation of North Africa Programs and Marcoux Report, 1975-1976 (Box 19)
  - "Report on the North African Regional Program, 1970-1971" by the Population Council Re: Ford Foundation Grant, 1972 (Box 19)
  - Population -- General -- Alumni Association, ENAP, Morrocco, 1973 (Box 19)
  - Population -- General Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 19)
  - Population -- General Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 19)
  - Population -- General -- Other Agencies, Jun 1974-1976 (Box 19)
  - Population -- General -- Other Agencies -- Women's International Forum on Population and Development and Ford Foundation International Division Women's Programs, 1973-1974 (Box 19)
  - Population -- General -- Other Agencies -- Resource Institutions (Harvard Center for Population Studies), 1973 (Box 19)
  - Population -- General -- Other Agencies -- Rennes, School of Health, 1973-1974 (Box 19)